JSON IN KNACK
1 After Topic List Save:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.1","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell structure","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.2","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Biological membranes","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.3","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.1","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.2","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.3","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.1","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.2","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"5.1","type":"topic","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"}]

field_3000 (Color Mapping) - {"Biology":"#3cb44b"}

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1742987541431_nxohqy8","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids"},{"id":"2.1","name":"Cells: Cell structure"},{"id":"2.2","name":"Cells: Biological membranes"},{"id":"2.3","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis"},{"id":"3.1","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio"},{"id":"3.2","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish"},{"id":"3.3","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects"},{"id":"4.1","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome"},{"id":"4.2","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis"},{"id":"5.1","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T11:12:21.431Z"}]

field_3086 - []

2 After Generating and and Adding to Bank:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":false,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.243Z"},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.1","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell structure","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.2","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Biological membranes","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.3","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.1","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.2","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.3","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.1","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.2","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"5.1","type":"topic","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"card_1742987570425_0_gr6210zz7","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the primary function of proteins in living organisms?","answer":"Correct Answer: b) B. Structural support","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Proteins play a crucial role in providing structural support to cells and tissues. They make up components such as muscles, hair, and nails.","additionalInfo":"Proteins play a crucial role in providing structural support to cells and tissues. They make up components such as muscles, hair, and nails.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Energy storage","B. Structural support","C. DNA replication","D. Waste elimination"],"savedOptions":["A. Energy storage","B. Structural support","C. DNA replication","D. Waste elimination"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_1_gr6daq9nd","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which of the following is NOT a type of protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: b) B. Nucleic acids","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Nucleic acids, such as DNA and RNA, are not proteins but rather another type of biological molecule responsible for storing and transmitting genetic information.","additionalInfo":"Nucleic acids, such as DNA and RNA, are not proteins but rather another type of biological molecule responsible for storing and transmitting genetic information.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Enzymes","B. Nucleic acids","C. Antibodies","D. Hormones"],"savedOptions":["A. Enzymes","B. Nucleic acids","C. Antibodies","D. Hormones"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_2_8neg15mma","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the basic unit of a protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: a) A. Amino acid","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins. When amino acids link together in a specific sequence, they form a protein molecule.","additionalInfo":"Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins. When amino acids link together in a specific sequence, they form a protein molecule.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Amino acid","B. Nucleotide","C. Monosaccharide","D. Fatty acid"],"savedOptions":["A. Amino acid","B. Nucleotide","C. Monosaccharide","D. Fatty acid"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_3_vd88qqvzx","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which level of protein structure is determined by the sequence of amino acids?","answer":"Correct Answer: a) A. Primary structure","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"The primary structure of a protein is determined by the sequence of amino acids in the polypeptide chain. This sequence is crucial for the overall structure and function of the protein.","additionalInfo":"The primary structure of a protein is determined by the sequence of amino acids in the polypeptide chain. This sequence is crucial for the overall structure and function of the protein.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Primary structure","B. Secondary structure","C. Tertiary structure","D. Quaternary structure"],"savedOptions":["A. Primary structure","B. Secondary structure","C. Tertiary structure","D. Quaternary structure"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570427_4_woqo30wqq","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which of the following factors can denature a protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: d) D. All of the above","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Proteins can be denatured, or lose their shape and function, due to various factors including changes in pH, temperature, and exposure to chemicals. This can disrupt their biological activity.","additionalInfo":"Proteins can be denatured, or lose their shape and function, due to various factors including changes in pH, temperature, and exposure to chemicals. This can disrupt their biological activity.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Change in pH","B. Change in temperature","C. Exposure to chemicals","D. All of the above"],"savedOptions":["A. Change in pH","B. Change in temperature","C. Exposure to chemicals","D. All of the above"],"topicId":"1.2"}]

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1742987541431_nxohqy8","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids"},{"id":"2.1","name":"Cells: Cell structure"},{"id":"2.2","name":"Cells: Biological membranes"},{"id":"2.3","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis"},{"id":"3.1","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio"},{"id":"3.2","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish"},{"id":"3.3","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects"},{"id":"4.1","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome"},{"id":"4.2","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis"},{"id":"5.1","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T11:12:21.431Z"}]


field_3000 -{"Biology":"#3cb44b"}

field_3086 - [{"cardId":"card_1742987570425_0_gr6210zz7","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_1_gr6daq9nd","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_2_8neg15mma","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_3_vd88qqvzx","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570427_4_woqo30wqq","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"}]

2 After Clicking Save Button:
field_2979 - [{"id":"1.1","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267330","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.2","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#267347","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":false,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.243Z"},{"id":"1.3","type":"topic","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#26735e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.1","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell structure","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#29797b","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.2","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Biological membranes","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#2f6f8e","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"2.3","type":"topic","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#365ea1","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.1","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#3c45b4","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.2","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#6348c2","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"3.3","type":"topic","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#945bc8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.1","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#be6ecf","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"4.2","type":"topic","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d581ca","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"5.1","type":"topic","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","color":"#d98cb8","baseColor":"#3cb44b","subjectColor":"#3cb44b","cards":[],"isShell":true,"isEmpty":true,"created":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z","updated":"2025-03-26T11:12:26.391Z"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.380Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.380Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:13:35.381Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:13:35.381Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:14:35.360Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:14:35.360Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:15:35.358Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:15:35.358Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:35.367Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:35.367Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:36.366Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:36.366Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"1.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267330","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.1"},{"id":"1.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#267347","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"1.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Lipids","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#26735e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"1.3"},{"id":"2.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell structure","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#29797b","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.1"},{"id":"2.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Biological membranes","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#2f6f8e","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.2"},{"id":"2.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#365ea1","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"2.3"},{"id":"3.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#3c45b4","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.1"},{"id":"3.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#6348c2","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.2"},{"id":"3.3","subject":"Biology","topic":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#945bc8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"3.3"},{"id":"4.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#be6ecf","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.1"},{"id":"4.2","subject":"Biology","topic":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d581ca","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"4.2"},{"id":"5.1","subject":"Biology","topic":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topicPriority":0,"question":"","answer":"","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"","additionalInfo":"","cardColor":"#d98cb8","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:18:52.125Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:18:52.125Z","type":"topic","questionType":"short_answer","topicId":"5.1"},{"id":"card_1742987570425_0_gr6210zz7","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the primary function of proteins in living organisms?","answer":"Correct Answer: b) B. Structural support","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Proteins play a crucial role in providing structural support to cells and tissues. They make up components such as muscles, hair, and nails.","additionalInfo":"Proteins play a crucial role in providing structural support to cells and tissues. They make up components such as muscles, hair, and nails.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Energy storage","B. Structural support","C. DNA replication","D. Waste elimination"],"savedOptions":["A. Energy storage","B. Structural support","C. DNA replication","D. Waste elimination"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_1_gr6daq9nd","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which of the following is NOT a type of protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: b) B. Nucleic acids","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Nucleic acids, such as DNA and RNA, are not proteins but rather another type of biological molecule responsible for storing and transmitting genetic information.","additionalInfo":"Nucleic acids, such as DNA and RNA, are not proteins but rather another type of biological molecule responsible for storing and transmitting genetic information.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Enzymes","B. Nucleic acids","C. Antibodies","D. Hormones"],"savedOptions":["A. Enzymes","B. Nucleic acids","C. Antibodies","D. Hormones"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_2_8neg15mma","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"What is the basic unit of a protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: a) A. Amino acid","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins. When amino acids link together in a specific sequence, they form a protein molecule.","additionalInfo":"Amino acids are the building blocks of proteins. When amino acids link together in a specific sequence, they form a protein molecule.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Amino acid","B. Nucleotide","C. Monosaccharide","D. Fatty acid"],"savedOptions":["A. Amino acid","B. Nucleotide","C. Monosaccharide","D. Fatty acid"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570426_3_vd88qqvzx","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which level of protein structure is determined by the sequence of amino acids?","answer":"Correct Answer: a) A. Primary structure","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"The primary structure of a protein is determined by the sequence of amino acids in the polypeptide chain. This sequence is crucial for the overall structure and function of the protein.","additionalInfo":"The primary structure of a protein is determined by the sequence of amino acids in the polypeptide chain. This sequence is crucial for the overall structure and function of the protein.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Primary structure","B. Secondary structure","C. Tertiary structure","D. Quaternary structure"],"savedOptions":["A. Primary structure","B. Secondary structure","C. Tertiary structure","D. Quaternary structure"],"topicId":"1.2"},{"id":"card_1742987570427_4_woqo30wqq","subject":"Biology","topic":"Biological molecules: Proteins","examBoard":"General","examType":"Course","topicPriority":0,"question":"Which of the following factors can denature a protein?","answer":"Correct Answer: d) D. All of the above","keyPoints":[],"detailedAnswer":"Proteins can be denatured, or lose their shape and function, due to various factors including changes in pH, temperature, and exposure to chemicals. This can disrupt their biological activity.","additionalInfo":"Proteins can be denatured, or lose their shape and function, due to various factors including changes in pH, temperature, and exposure to chemicals. This can disrupt their biological activity.","cardColor":"#ffe119","textColor":"","boxNum":1,"lastReviewed":null,"nextReviewDate":"2025-03-27T11:16:39.514Z","createdAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","updatedAt":"2025-03-26T11:16:39.514Z","questionType":"multiple_choice","options":["A. Change in pH","B. Change in temperature","C. Exposure to chemicals","D. All of the above"],"savedOptions":["A. Change in pH","B. Change in temperature","C. Exposure to chemicals","D. All of the above"],"topicId":"1.2"}]

field_3011 - [{"id":"list_1742987541431_nxohqy8","subject":"Biology","examBoard":"AQA","examType":"A-Level","topics":[{"id":"1.1","name":"Biological molecules: Carbohydrates"},{"id":"1.2","name":"Biological molecules: Proteins"},{"id":"1.3","name":"Biological molecules: Lipids"},{"id":"2.1","name":"Cells: Cell structure"},{"id":"2.2","name":"Cells: Biological membranes"},{"id":"2.3","name":"Cells: Cell division, mitosis, and meiosis"},{"id":"3.1","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Surface area to volume ratio"},{"id":"3.2","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in fish"},{"id":"3.3","name":"Organisms exchange substances with their environment: Gas exchange in insects"},{"id":"4.1","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: DNA and the Genome"},{"id":"4.2","name":"Genetic information, variation, and relationships between organisms: RNA and Protein synthesis"},{"id":"5.1","name":"[Optional] Biodiversity, evolution, and disease: Communicable diseases"}],"lastUpdated":"2025-03-26T11:12:21.431Z"}]

field_3000 - {"Biology":"#3cb44b"}

field_3086 - [{"cardId":"card_1742987570425_0_gr6210zz7","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_1_gr6daq9nd","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_2_8neg15mma","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570426_3_vd88qqvzx","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"},{"cardId":"card_1742987570427_4_woqo30wqq","lastReviewed":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z","nextReviewDate":"2025-03-26T11:16:40.244Z"}]

